Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Chemistry, Waymouth Group, Records SC1263
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Department of Chemistry, Waymouth Group, Records
1989-2015
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Waymouth, Robert M.
Stanford University. Department of Chemistry. Waymouth Group
SC1263
90 Linear Feet (60 cartons)
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Administrative transfer, 2016.
Biographical / Historical
Led by Robert Eckles Swain Professor in Chemistry Robert Waymouth, the Waymouth group applies mechanistic principles to develop homogeneous catalysts for the selective synthesis of both macromolecules and fine chemicals. Particular areas of interest include catalytic polymerization reactions, the development of organocatalytic polymerization strategies, selective oxidation catalysis, and the synthesis and properties of cyclic polymers. http://web.stanford.edu/group/waymouth/Waymouth_Research_Group/Home.html
Scope and Contents
Series consists of lab notebooks. Series 1 consists of Spectra Notebooks & and Series 2 consists of Waymouth Lab Notebooks. Most are labeled by name of researcher.
Catalysis; Chemistry.; Waymouth, Robert M.; Stanford University. Department of Chemistry. Waymouth Group; Waymouth, Robert M.; Stanford University. Department of Chemistry. Waymouth Group
- Spectra Notebooks, Series 1
  - Alexandrina Rusu - Zn Ipr2, 2011 (Box 1)
  - Alexandrina Rusu - Philips system, 2011 (Box 1)
  - Alexandrina Rusu - Philips system, 2012 (Box 1)
  - Alexandrina Rusu - DR NMR Spectra, 2010 (Box 1)
  - Alexandrina Rusu - PONROP, 2011 (Box 1)
  - Wonhee Jeong - NMR, 2005 (Box 1)
  - Sang Jin Jeon - SJ 2 NMR and MS, 2006 (Box 1)
  - Sang Jin Jeon - SJ 3 NMR and MS, 2007 (Box 2)
  - Sang Jin Jeon - SJ 4 NMR and MS, 2007 (Box 2)
  - Eu Ji Shin - AJ, 2007 (Box 2)
  - JM - Summer Student, 2009 (Box 2)
  - Olivier Coulembier - 13C 1H NMR Spectra OLCO 1A, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Olivier Coulembier - Olivier GPC, GC-MS, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Olivier Coulembier - Report, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Olivier Coulembier - Olivier NMR-1 Second Part, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Wonhee Jeong - GPC, 2007 (Box 2)
  - Alice Lincoln - ALL-I Ethylene 1-hexene copolymerization, 2003 (Box 2)
  - Alice Lincoln - ALL-2, 2003 (Box 2)
  - Alice Lincoln - ALL-3, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Melanie (MZ )- NMR-1, 2005 (Box 3)
  - Melanie (MZ) - NMR-2, 2005 (Box 3)
  - Ben Katz - Spectral Data New Compounds, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Darcy Culkin - Characterization DC-5-5, 2006 (Box 3)
  - Darcy Culkin - Characterization-DC-3-99-4-100, 2006 (Box 3)
  - Szilard Csihony - Spectra V-VI, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Szilard Csihony - Spectra III-IV, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Szilard Csihony - Spectra V-VI, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Characterization - DC-3-5-DC-3-98, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Nahrain Kamber - NEK-I, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Nahrain Kamber - NEK-II Spectra, 2003 (Box 4)
  - Nahrain Kamber - Lab Notebook #3 Spectra NEK-III, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Nahrain Kamber - NEK-IV, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Nahrain Kamber - NEK-V, 2005 (Box 4)
  - Nahrain Kamber - NEK-IV-2 Spectra, 2005 (Box 4)
  - Nahrain Kamber - NEK NMR NEK-VII -1, 2005 (Box 4)
  - Nahrain Kamber - NEK VII-2 Spectra, 2006 (Box 5)
  - Karen Sun - KS-I, 2005 (Box 5)
  - Karen Sun - KS I/II, 2007 (Box 5)
  - Karen Sun - KS III, 2007 (Box 5)
  - Karen Sun - KS IV, 2007 (Box 5)
  - Karen Sun - KS V, 2008 (Box 5)
  - Karen Sun - KS:Cr-Zn Transmetallation, 2008 (Box 5)
  - Karen Sun - KS: PNNP-metal, 2008 (Box 5)
  - Karen Sun - KS ES 120 deg C, 2006 (Box 5)
  - Karen Sun - KS: ES 70 deg C, 2006 (Box 5)
  - Sarah Reybuck SER-I Spectra, 1999 (Box 5)
  - Sarah Reybuck SER-II Spectra, 2000 (Box 5)
  - Sarah Reybuck SER-III Spectra, 2001 (Box 5)
  - Sarah Reybuck SER-IV Spectra, 2001 (Box 6)
  - Sarah Reybuck SER-V Spectra, 2002 (Box 6)
  - Sarah Reybuck SET-VI Spectra, 2002 (Box 6)
  - Wendy Fan NMR (Synthesis): WF-I, II (1998) (Box 6)
  - Wendy Fan NMR (Polymer): WF-I, II, III (1998 - 1999) (Box 6)
  - Wendy Fan WF-VI-polymer NMR, 2000 (Box 6)
  - Wendy Fan GPC: WF (1998 - (Box 6)
  - Wendy Fan WF-V, VI- NMR, 1999 (Box 6)
  - Wendy Fan WF-IV-NMR, 1999 (Box 6)
  - Wendy Fan WF-V-polymer NMR, 1999 (Box 6)
  - Steven M. Banik Spectra #2, 2010 (Box 6)
  - APD 2003 (Box 6)
  - Kuo-Wei Huang II, III, IV, 2001 (Box 7)
  - Kuo-Wei Huang 2 - 2, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Joyce Hung III, 2001 (Box 7)
  - Joyce Hung III, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Joyce Hung III, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Joyce Hung I, 1999 (Box 7)
  - Joyce Hung II, 2000 (Box 7)
  - Fernando Gomez NMR-II, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Fernando Gomez NMR-I, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Fernando Gomez NMR, 2001 (Box 8)
  - Fernando Gomez GC-MS, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Adrien Lavoie NMR DSC GPC Book III, 2003 (Box 8)
  - Adrien Lavoie NMR-III, 2003 (Box 8)
  - Adrien Lavoie NMR Book 4, 2003 (Box 8)
  - Bon Jun Koo NMR-I, 2007 (Box 8)
  - Ariel Yeh GC-MS, 2011 (Box 8)
  - Brad Kraft Spectra I II, 2002 (Box 8)
  - Nahrain Kamber NEK-VII-Spectra, 2007 (Box 8)
  - Madalyn Radlauer NMR GC-MS Spectra #2, 2007 (Box 8)
  - Tong Chu Tong Chu GCMS/DSC, 2002 (Box 9)
  - Fernando Gomez NMR III-IV, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Michaela Dankova EH copolymers DSC, NMR, 1999 (Box 9)
  - Michaela Dankova NMR MD III, 2000 (Box 9)
  - Michaela Dankova ditBu paper data, 2002 (Box 9)
  - Pinar Kilickiran P. Kilickiran NMR spectra, 2002 (Box 9)
  - Michaela Dankova MD-I-spectra, 1998 (Box 9)
  - Masami Kamigato MK GPC NMR-3, 1998 (Box 9)
  - Ned Bowden NED 4-6, 2002 (Box 9)
  - Mark Krejchi MK tensile test, 1996 (Box 9)
  - Ned Bowden Ned 2 catalyst prep, 2000 (Box 9)
  - Madalyn Radlauer NMR, GCMS, 2008 (Box 10)
  - Ned Bowden Ned 1 NMR, 2000 (Box 10)
  - Ned Bowden Ned 3 NMR, 2001 (Box 10)
  - Ron Painter - RMP IV, 2010 (Box 10)
  - Ron Painter - RMP IV PART 2, 2010 (Box 10)
  - Yasuhito Tsujii - YT-1 NMR, 2006 (Box 10)
  - YF-1 NMR, 2001 (Box 10)
  - Mahesh Mahanthappa - MKM-6, 2001 (Box 10)
  - Margarete LeClerc - NMR, 1996 (Box 10)
  - SM-2 NMR, 2003 (Box 11)
  - IMA - NMR, 1999 (Box 11)
  - Madalyn Radlauer - NMR-3, 2007 (Box 11)
  - Haley Brown - DSC, TGA, 2008 (Box 11)
  - Bridgett Payne - BP-1 NMR, 2005 (Box 11)
  - FJ-1 NMR, 2004 (Box 11)
  - Yasuhito Tsujii - YT-2 NMR, 2006 (Box 11)
  - SM-1 NMR, 2002 (Box 11)
  - Mahesh Mahanthappa - MKM NMR 8, 2002 (Box 11)
  - Mahesh Mahanthappa - MKM NMR 1-3, 1999 (Box 12)
  - Mahesh Mahanthappa - MKM NMR 4-5, 2000 (Box 12)
  - Mahesh Mahanthappa - MKM NMR 7,9, 2002 (Box 12)
  - Nahrain Kamber - NEK-1 NMR, GPC, 2005 (Box 12)
  - Yasuhito Tsujii - YT-0,1, 2006 (Box 12)
  - Ariel Yeh - AY-1, 2011 (Box 12)
  - Steven M. Banik - SMB-1, 2010 (Box 12)
  - Sungkwan Kim - KSK-1 NMR, 2013 (Box 12)
  - GP NMR, 2008 (Box 12)
  - KAK NMR, 2005 (Box 12)
  - KAK NMR 2, 2005 (Box 12)
  - Mark Krejchi - DSC, xray, 1996 (Box 13)
  - Ari Esters - AQE NMR, 2014 (Box 13)
  - Vilhelm Olsson - VO-1 NMR, DSC, 2011 (Box 13)
  - Vilhelm Olsson - VO-2 NMR, 2011 (Box 13)
  - Vilhelm Olsson - VO-3,4 NMR, 2012 (Box 13)
  - Hayley Brown - 1, 2008 (Box 13)
  - Hayley Brown - 2, 2008 (Box 13)
  - Hayley Brown - 3, 2009 (Box 14)
  - Hayley Brown - 5, 2010 (Box 14)
  - Hayley Brown - 6, 2010 (Box 14)
  - Hayley Brown - 7, 2011 (Box 14)
  - Hayley Brown - 8, 2011 (Box 14)
  - Hayley Brown - 9, 2012 (Box 15)
  - Hayley Brown - 10, 2012 (Box 15)
  - Hayley Brown - 11, 2013 (Box 15)
  - Tyler Stukenbroeker - 3, 2012 (Box 15)
  - Tyler Stukenbroeker - 4,5, 2013 (Box 15)
  - Tyler Stukenbroeker - 6, 2014 (Box 15)
  - Matt Kieswetter - 1, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Matt Kieswetter - 2, 2006 (Box 15)
  - Matt Kieswetter - 3, 2007 (Box 15)
  - Matt Kieswetter - 4, 2007 (Box 16)
  - Matt Kieswetter - 5, 2008 (Box 16)
  - Matt Kieswetter - 6, 2009 (Box 16)
  - Matt Kieswetter - 7, 2009 (Box 16)
  - Matt Kieswetter - 8, 2010 (Box 16)
  - Matt Kieswetter - 1 PART 2, 2006 (Box 16)
  - RLW NMR (Box 16)
  - RLW NMR 2 (Box 16)
  - Sam Borkowsky SB02 NMR, 1992 (Box 17)
  - Jan Schultz SJ1 NMR, 2002 (Box 17)
  - "LL" NMR (Box 17)
  - Hyunuk Kim - NMR, GPC, MS 1, 2010 (Box 17)
  - Hyunuk Kim - NMR, GPC, MS 2, 2010 (Box 17)
  - Binia Thomaszewski - NMR1, 2007 (Box 17)
  - Bridgett Payne - NMR 1,2, 2004 (Box 17)
  - Binia Thomaszewski NMR2, 2008 (Box 18)
  - Ray G NMR GPC (Box 18)
  - Sam Borkowsky NMR 1, 1992 (Box 18)
  - Frank Joese NMR GPC DSC, 2005 (Box 18)
  - Justin Edwards NMR GPC, 2010 (Box 18)
  - Kristen Brownell - NMR 2, 2011 (Box 18)
  - Kristen Brownell - NMR 6, 2012 (Box 18)
  - APD - NMR GPC, 1997 (Box 19)
  - APD - NMR 3,4 (Box 19)
  - Kristen Brownell - NMR 3, 2011 (Box 19)
  - Kristen Brownell - NMR 4, 2011 (Box 19)
  - Kristen Brownell - NMR 7, 2012 (Box 19)
  - APD - NMR 2 (Box 19)
  - Kristen Brownell - NMR 5, 2012 (Box 19)
  - APD - NMR 5,6 (Box 20)
  - Tyler Stukenbroeker NMR 1, 2, 2011 (Box 20)
  - Liz Tanzini/Kieswetter NMR 4B, 2010 (Box 20)
  - Kristen Brownell NMR 1, 2011 (Box 20)
  - Eugene Chia NMR GPC, 2013 (Box 20)
  - Nick R. Conley NMR 2, 2009 (Box 20)
  - Darcy Culkin NMR GPC, 2004 (Box 20)
  - Eun Ji GPC, 2008 (Box 20)
  - David Pearson NMR 1, 2006 (Box 21)
  - David Pearson NMR 2, 2006 (Box 21)
  - David Pearson NMR 4, 2007 (Box 21)
  - David Pearson NMR 5, 2007 (Box 21)
  - David Pearson NMR 6, 2007 (Box 21)
  - Eun Ji NMR GPC, 2008 (Box 22)
  - Eun Ji NMR GPC 2, 2007-2008 (Box 22)
  - Darcy Culkin NMR 1, 2005 (Box 22)
  - WLN NMR 1, 2008 (Box 22)
  - Eun Ji NMR 6, 2010 (Box 22)
  - Justin Edwards book 2, 2010 (Box 22)
  - Soeren Randoll NMR 1, 2009 (Box 22)
  - Eun Ji NMR 3, 2007 (Box 22)
  - Eun Ji NMR 4, 2009 (Box 22)
  - David Pearson NMR 7/8, 2009 (Box 23)
  - David Pearson NMR 9, 2009 (Box 23)
  - David Pearson NMR 10, 2009 (Box 23)
  - Nahrain Kamber NMR 5, 2005 (Box 23)
  - Nahrain Kamber NMR 6, 2005 (Box 23)
  - Sam Borkowsky NMR 1, 1992 (Box 23)
  - Michael Driver Misc, 1998 (Box 23)
  - Liz Tanzini/Kieswetter 3a, 2010 (Box 24)
  - Liz Tanzini/Kieswetter 2b, 2010 (Box 24)
  - Liz Tanzini/Kieswetter 2a, 2010 (Box 24)
  - Liz Tanzini/Kieswetter 1, 2010 (Box 24)
  - Liz Tanzini/Kieswetter 3b, 2010 (Box 24)
  - Liz Tanzini/Kieswetter 4a, 2010 (Box 24)
  - Liz Tanzini/Kieswetter 5a, 2010 (Box 24)
  - Soeren Randoll NMR 2, 2009 (Box 25)
  - MBF (Box 25)
  - Brad Kraft NMR 3, 2003 (Box 25)
  - Liz Tanzini/Kieswetter Regioirregular, 2010 (Box 25)
  - Liz Tanzini/Kieswetter P.P. Regio, 2010 (Box 25)
  - Liz Tanzini/Kieswetter excel 6, 2009 (Box 25)
  - Madalyn Radlauer Spectra 1, 2008 (Box 25)
  - Andrew Ingram Notebook 1, 2015 (Box 25)
  - Ben Katz NMR 1, 2005 (Box 25)
  - Ben Katz NMR 2, 2005 (Box 25)
  - Marc Scholten NMR 1, 2006 (Box 26)
  - Marc Scholten NMR 2,3, 2006 (Box 26)
  - Marc Scholten GTP Project, 2006 (Box 26)
  - Marc Scholten TBD Project, 2006 (Box 26)
  - Marc Scholten ATRP, Aldol, GPC, 2006 (Box 26)
  - M. Ho NMR, GPC, 1999 (Box 27)
  - M. Ho NMR 2, 1999 (Box 27)
  - H. Nakamura NMR 1, 1998 (Box 27)
  - G. Brown NMR, 1997 (Box 27)
  - B. Kwan NMR, GC-MS, 1999 (Box 27)
  - M. Finze NMR 1, 2000 (Box 28)
  - M. Finze NMR 2, 2000 (Box 28)
  - M. Finze NMR 3, 2000 (Box 28)
  - M. Finze NMR 4, 2000 (Box 28)
  - M. Finze NMR 5, 2000 (Box 28)
  - M. Finze NMR 6, 2000 (Box 29)
  - M. Finze NMR 7, 2000 (Box 29)
  - JK Lau NMR, 2002 (Box 29)
  - Simon Stelzig NMR, DSC, GPC 1, 2005 (Box 30)
  - Wendy Fan NMR, GPC, 1998 (Box 30)
  - Tong Choo NMR 1, 1998 (Box 30)
  - Tong Choo NMR 2, 1998 (Box 30)
  - Tong Choo NMR 3, 1998 (Box 30)
  - Tong Choo NMR 4, 1998 (Box 30)
  - Jennifer Polse NMR, 1994 (Box 30)
  - Jennifer Polse XRD 1, 1994 (Box 30)
  - Zhong-Ren Chen GPC, 1999 (Box 30)
  - SMC Various, 1993 (Box 30)
  - Jeff Brown NMR 1, 1990 (Box 31)
  - Jeff Brown NMR 2, 1990 (Box 31)
  - Jeff Brown NMR 3, 1990 (Box 31)
  - Jeff Brown NMR 4, 1990 (Box 31)
  - Jeff Brown NMR 5, 1990 (Box 31)
  - Michael Driver NMR/GPC, 1999 (Box 32)
  - Bridgett Payne DSC/GPC, 2006 (Box 32)
  - Bruce, Michelle D. MDB, 1994 (Box 33)
  - Bruce, Michelle D. MDB, 1994 (Box 33)
  - Bruce, Michelle D. MDB, 1995 (Box 33)
  - Bruce, Michelle D. MDB, 1996 (Box 33)
  - Mike Kesti V, 1991 (Box 33)
  - Mike Kesti VI, 1991 (Box 33)
  - Mike Kesti V, 1991 (Box 33)
  - Mike Kesti IV, 1991 (Box 33)
  - Mike Kesti III, 1990 (Box 33)
  - Mike Kesti II, 1990 (Box 33)
  - Mike Kesti VIII, 1992 (Box 33)
  - Mike Kesti II, 1990 (Box 33)
  - McKnight, Andrew II, 1994 (Box 34)
  - McKnight, Andrew XI, 1993 (Box 34)
  - McKnight, Andrew XII, 1997 (Box 34)
  - McKnight, Andrew XII, 1998 (Box 34)
  - Dan Millward DM2, NMR, 1995 (Box 34)
  - Dan Millward DM3, NMR, 1996 (Box 34)
  - Dan Millward DM6,7, NMR, 1996-1997 (Box 34)
  - Dan Millward DM1, NMR, 1995 (Box 34)
  - Dan Millward DM10-14, NMR, 1997-1998 (Box 34)
  - Dan Millward DM8,9, NMR, 1997 (Box 34)
  - Dan Millward DM4, NMR, 1996 (Box 35)
  - Michael Driver MSD-II, 1999 (Box 35)
  - Michael Driver NMR, 1993 (Box 35)
  - Arndt Meyer AM-1, NMR, 1998 (Box 35)
  - McSwain, Hugh, 1993 (Box 35)
  - Banovetz, John, 1992 (Box 35)
  - Banovetz, John, 1992 (Box 35)
  - Banovetz, John, 1993 (Box 35)
  - Banovetz, John, 1993 (Box 35)
  - Miller, Steve, 1994 (Box 35)
  - Peter Fox PAF-1, 1998 (Box 36)
  - Reiko Leno RL-I, 1999 (Box 36)
  - Coates, Geoff W., 1992 (Box 36)
  - Coates, Geoff W., 1992 (Box 36)
  - Coates, Geoff W., 1993 (Box 36)
  - Coates, Geoff W., 1993 (Box 36)
  - Reiko Leno RL-II, 1999 (Box 37)
  - Christopher, Tagge II, 1996 (Box 37)
  - Christopher, Tagge III, 1997 (Box 37)
  - Christopher, Tagge IV, 1997 (Box 37)
  - Dris, Haroula HD-8B, 1995 (Box 37)
  - Dris, Haroula Desert Analytics, 1996 (Box 37)
  - Dris, Haroula HD-8A, 1995 (Box 37)
  - Dris, Haroula HD-VII, 1995 (Box 37)
  - Dris, Haroula HD-VI, 1995 (Box 37)
  - Dris, Haroula HD-IV, 1994 (Box 37)
  - Dris, Haroula HD-9B, 1996 (Box 37)
  - John Banovetz IV, 1993 (Box 38)
  - John Banovetz VII, 1993 (Box 38)
  - John Banovetz V, 1992 (Box 38)
  - Yu-Ling Hsiao IX, 1994 (Box 38)
  - Yu-Ling Hsiao VIII, 1994 (Box 38)
  - Yu-Ling Hsiao VI, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Yu-Ling Hsiao VI, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Yu-Ling Hsiao VII, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Yu-Ling Hsiao V, VI, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Yu-Ling Hsiao V, 1992 (Box 38)
  - Dris, Haroula 7, 1995 (Box 38)
  - Dris, Haroula III, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Dris, Haroula II, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Dris, Haroula II, 1992 (Box 38)
  - Yu-Ling Hsiao YLH, IR, UV, 1992-1994 (Box 39)
  - Yu-Ling Hsiao YLH-IV, 1992 (Box 39)
  - Yu-Ling Hsiao YLH-I, 1991 (Box 39)
  - Yu-Ling Hsiao YLH-II, 1991 (Box 39)
  - Yu-Ling Hsiao YLH-I+II, 1991 (Box 39)
  - Yu-Ling Hsiao YLH-VII, 1993 (Box 39)
  - Yu-Ling Hsiao YLH-III, 1992 (Box 39)
  - Yu-Ling Hsiao YLH, DSC, 1993 (Box 39)
  - Yu-Ling Hsiao YLH-III+IV, 1992 (Box 39)
  - Yu-Ling Hsiao fluoresence, 1992-1995 (Box 39)
  - Yu-Ling Hsiao YLH-VIII+IX, 1993 (Box 39)
  - Yu-Ling Hsiao YLH, IR, UV, 1992 (Box 39)
  - Yu-Ling Hsiao YLH, IR, UV, 1993 (Box 39)
  - Mike Kesti MK-VIII, 1994 (Box 39)
  - LaPointe, Anne M. AML, NMR, 1989 (Box 39)
  - Knight, Kyle, 1992 (Box 40)
  - Knight, Kyle Transmetallation - KKV, 1992 (Box 40)
  - Knight, Kyle KK Miscellaneous NMR Study, 1992 (Box 40)
  - Knight, Kyle KK I to II, 1990 (Box 40)
  - Knight, Kyle KK-II-51 to IV-007, 1990 (Box 40)
  - Knight, Kyle KK-IV-09 to V, 1991 (Box 40)
  - Knight, Kyle KK-IV, 1991 (Box 40)
  - Hauptman, Elizabeth EH Notebook-I-A, 1994 (Box 40)
  - Hauptman, Elizabeth Notebook-III-B, 1995 (Box 40)
  - Hauptman, Elizabeth Notebook-III-A, 1995 (Box 40)
  - Hauptman, Elizabeth Notebook-II-B, 1995 (Box 40)
  - Hauptman, Elizabeth Notebook-II-A, 1994 (Box 40)
  - Hauptman, Elizabeth Notebook-I-B, 1994 (Box 40)
  - Josuweit, Frauke Frauke Josuweit, 1989 (Box 40)
  - Waymouth, Robert M. BMW, 1990 (Box 40)
  - Hollberg, T. T. Hollberg, 1991 (Box 40)
  - LaPointe, Anne M. AML-2, AML-3, 1990 (Box 41)
  - Luigi Resconi LR-I, 1989 (Box 41)
  - Luigi Resconi LR-1-120, 1990 (Box 41)
  - Luigi Resconi LR-1-120, 1989-1990 (Box 41)
  - David Wang DW-I, 1990 (Box 41)
  - Ulrike Wilschmeyer UW-I, 1990 (Box 41)
  - Ulrike Wilschmeyer UW-1, 1990 (Box 41)
  - Kevin Stein KSH-1, 1994 (Box 41)
  - Kevin Stein KSH-XVII, 1997 (Box 41)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin KHS6, 1995 (Box 42)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin KHS5, 1994 (Box 42)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin Elemental analysis, 1997 (Box 42)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin KHS16, 1997 (Box 42)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin KHS3, 1993 (Box 42)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin KHS6, 1996 (Box 42)
  - Kravchenko, Raisa RK4-7, 1996 (Box 42)
  - Kravchenko, Raisa RK4, 1996 (Box 43)
  - Kravchenko, Raisa RK6, 1996 (Box 43)
  - Kravchenko, Raisa RK4, 1999 (Box 43)
  - Kravchenko, Raisa RK3, 1995 (Box 43)
  - Kravchenko, Raisa RK2, 1995 (Box 43)
  - Kravchenko, Raisa RK7, 1997 (Box 43)
  - Lise, Anne DSC 1-24, 1991 (Box 44)
  - Lise, Anne DSC 25-58, 1991 (Box 44)
  - Lise, Anne DSC 59-90, 1991 (Box 44)
  - Lise, Anne DSC 91-106, 1991 (Box 44)
  - Lise, Anne DSC 107-139, 1991 (Box 44)
  - Lise, Anne DSC 140-187, 1991 (Box 44)
  - Lise, Anne NMR 140-187, 1993 (Box 44)
  - Lise, Anne NMR 188 -, 1994 (Box 44)
  - Lise, Anne NMR 1-24, 1990 (Box 44)
  - Lise, Anne NMR 25-58, 1990 (Box 44)
  - Lise, Anne NMR 59-90, 1991 (Box 44)
  - Lise, Anne NMR 90-139, 1992 (Box 44)
  - Lise, Anne Y. Hu NMR Data 1996 (Box 44)
  - Jenn Petoff JLMP: EH Copolmers, Notebook VII Part 2, 1998 (Box 45)
  - Jenn Petoff Waymouth ZrCl2 Crystal Structure, 1998 (Box 45)
  - Jenn Petoff ZrBr2 Crystal Strcutre, 1998 (Box 45)
  - Jenn Petoff Cp2ZrBz2, 1996 (Box 45)
  - Jenn Petoff JLMP: EH Copolymer Notebook VIII, 1998 (Box 45)
  - Jenn Petoff JLMP: EH Copolymers Supercritical Fractions, 1999 (Box 45)
  - Jenn Petoff JLMP:EH Copolymers Notebook IV, 1999 (Box 45)
  - Jenn Petoff Crystal Strcutres meso-MeSiZr2Cl2, 1997 (Box 45)
  - Jenn Petoff JLMP EP Copolymers + RK, 1997 (Box 45)
  - Jenn Petoff JLMP: EH Copolmers, Notebook VII Part 1, 1998 (Box 45)
  - Jenn Petoff JLMP: EH Copolmers, Notebook VI, 1998 (Box 45)
  - Jenn Petoff NMR Data Ligands and Complexes Notebooks V-VIII, 1998 (Box 45)
  - Jenn Petoff NMR Data Ligands and Complexes Notebooks V-VIII, 1997 (Box 45)
  - Jenn Petoff NMR Data Ligands and Complexes Notebooks V-VIII, 1996 (Box 45)
  - Jenn Petoff JMP PP Data Notebook VI - VIII, 1998 (Box 45)
  - Jenn Petoff Supercritical fluid fractions PP: Phase X, 1998 (Box 45)
  - Jenn Petoff JMP PP Data Notebook V, 1997 (Box 45)
  - Jenn Petoff JLMP Polymer Data Notebook IV, 1997 (Box 45)
  - Jenn Petoff JLMP PP Data Notebook II - III, 1997 (Box 45)
  - Margarete LeClerc NMR Spectra, 1998 (Box 46)
  - GC Data, 1998 (Box 46)
  - PW, NMR Data, 1997 (Box 46)
  - PW, NMR Data, 1998 (Box 46)
  - Chirag Shah C. Shah GC Data, 1997 (Box 46)
  - Masami Kamigato MK-NMR-2, 1997 (Box 46)
  - Masami Kamigato MK-NMR-1, 1997 (Box 46)
  - Y. Hu IR Spectra, 1995 (Box 46)
  - Y. Hu NMR Spectra, 1998 (Box 46)
  - Y. Hu Polymer Data, 1998 (Box 46)
  - Y. Hu NMR Data, 1995 (Box 46)
- Waymouth Lab Notebooks, Series 2
  - Bovino, Scott - 1, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Joseweit, Franke, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Abdulrahman, Maie, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Resconi, Luigi - 1, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Resconi, Luigi - 2, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Stromberg, Ove, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Ennevor, Sean J., 1989 (Box 1)
  - Bovino, Scott - 2, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Banovetz, John - 1, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Banovetz, John - 2, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Banovetz, John - 3, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Banovetz, John - 4, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Banovetz, John - 5, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Banovetz, John - 6, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Banovetz, John - 7, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Banovetz, John - 8 (IBM), 1993 (Box 1)
  - Banovetz, John - 9 (Spectra), 1993 (Box 1)
  - Hollberg - 1, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Wang, David - 1, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Wang, David - 2, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Fischer, David, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Coates, Geoff - 1, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Coates, Geoff - 2, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Coates, Geoff - 3, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Coates, Geoff - 4, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Kesti, Mike - 1, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Kesti, Mike - 2, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Kesti, Mike - 3, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Kesti, Mike - 4, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Kesti, Mike - 5, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Kesti, Mike - 6, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Kesti, Mike - 7, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Kesti, Mike - 8, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Kesti, Mike - 9, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Kesti, Mike - 10, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Knight, Kyle - 1, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Knight, Kyle - 2, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Knight, Kyle - 3, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Knight, Kyle - 4, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Knight, Kyle - 5, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Knight, Kyle - 6, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Knight, Kyle - 7, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Knight, Kyle - 8, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Knight, Kyle - 9, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Bruce, Michelle D. - 1, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Bruce, Michelle D. - 2, 1994 (Box 2)
  - Bruce, Michelle D. - 3, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Bruce, Michelle D. - 4, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Bruce, Michelle D. - 5, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Bruce, Michelle D. - 6, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Bruce, Michelle D. - 7, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Bruce, Michelle D. - 8, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Borkowksy, Sam - Autoclave Log Book, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Suzuki, Hiroshi - 1, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Borkowksy, Sam - 1, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Borkowksy, Sam - 2, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Borkowksy, Sam - 3, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Borkowksy, Sam - 4, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Hsiao, Yu-Ling - 1, 1991 (Box 3)
  - Hsiao, Yu-Ling - 2, 1991 (Box 3)
  - Hsiao, Yu-Ling - 3, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Hsiao, Yu-Ling - 4, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Hsiao, Yu-Ling - 5, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Hsiao, Yu-Ling - 6, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Hsiao, Yu-Ling - 7, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Hsiao, Yu-Ling - 8, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Hsiao, Yu-Ling - 9, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Miller, Steve - 1, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Miller, Steve - 2, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Miller, Steve - 3, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Miller, Steve - 4, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Mogstad, Anne-Lise - 1, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Mogstad, Anne-Lise - 2, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Mogstad, Anne-Lise - 3, 1991 (Box 3)
  - Mogstad, Anne-Lise - 4, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Mogstad, Anne-Lise - 5, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Mogstad, Anne-Lise - 6, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Newton, Joanna - 1, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Newton, Joanna - 2, 1995 (Box 3)
  - Zoumis, Kosta, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Krejchi, Mark T. - 1, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Krejchi, Mark T. - 2, 1995 (Box 3)
  - Krejchi, Mark T. - 3 (Box 3)
  - Krejchi, Mark T. - 4, 1995 (Box 3)
  - Krejchi, Mark T. - 5, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Dris, Haroula - 1, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Dris, Haroula - 2, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Dris, Haroula - 3, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Dris, Haroula - 4, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Dris, Haroula - 5, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Dris, Haroula - 6, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Dris, Haroula - 7, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Dris, Haroula - 8, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Dris, Haroula - 9, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Dris, Haroula - 10, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Stein, Kevin - 1, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Stein, Kevin - 2, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Stein, Kevin - 3, 1992 (Box 4)
  - Stein, Kevin - 4, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Stein, Kevin - 5, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Stein, Kevin - 6, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Stein, Kevin - 7 (Box 4)
  - Stein, Kevin - 8, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Hauptman, Elizabeth - 1, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Hauptman, Elizabeth - 2, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Hauptman, Elizabeth - 3, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Kravchenko, Raisa - 1, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Kravchenko, Raisa - 2, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Kravchenko, Raisa - 3, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Kravchenko, Raisa - 4, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Kravchenko, Raisa - 5, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Kravchenko, Raisa - 6, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Kravchenko, Raisa - 7, 1997 (Box 4)
  - McKnight, Andrew - 1, 1993 (Box 4)
  - McKnight, Andrew - 2, 1994 (Box 4)
  - McKnight, Andrew - 3, 1994 (Box 4)
  - McKnight, Andrew - 4, 1995 (Box 4)
  - McKnight, Andrew - 5, 1994 (Box 4)
  - McKnight, Andrew - 6, 1995 (Box 5)
  - McKnight, Andrew - 7, 1996 (Box 5)
  - McKnight, Andrew - 8, 1997 (Box 5)
  - McKnight, Andrew - 9, 1997 (Box 5)
  - McKnight, Andrew - 10, 1997 (Box 5)
  - McKnight, Andrew - 11, 1997 (Box 5)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin - 1, 1993 (Box 5)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin - 2, 1993 (Box 5)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin - 3, 1994 (Box 5)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin - 4, 1994 (Box 5)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin - 5, 1994 (Box 5)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin - 6, 1994 (Box 5)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin - 7, 1995 (Box 5)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin - 8, 1995 (Box 5)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin - 9, 1995 (Box 5)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin - 10, 1995 (Box 5)